RYAN DELA VICTORIA

Las Vegas, NV • 831-920-7329 • rdelavictoria4@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/rdelavictoria/

Professional Summary

Highly motivated individual that possess a SECRET clearance with 9 years of experience and proven knowledge of acute care facility, ambulatory care, emergency response, trauma response medical informatics and medical IT. Received higher education in Information Technology. Currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science in Cyber Security and Information Assurance from Western Governors University.

Skills

- Proces Improvement
- Operations oversight
- Electronic Health Records Expert; MHS Genesis
- Critical Thinker
- Experience in high stress environments
- Military Health Care Information Systems

Work History

Clinic Supervisor, 06/2018 to Current

California Medical Detachment, Presidio of Monterey - Presidio of Monterey, CA

- Supervises 20 military and 100 civilian staff at the Presidio of Monterey Army Health Clinic.
- Facilitates enduring MHS Genesis related training.
- Coordinated CBT and ILT training of all clinical staff prior to MHS Genesis launch.
- Implementation of MHS Genesis; DHMSM adopted clinical processes as best practices.
- Delivered effective onboarding and training to new and existing employees and cross-trained staff members in other job roles to maximize coverage.
- Assisted with project planning and execution of research.

Squad Leader, 06/2015 to 06/2018

1-503rd Infantry Battalion 173rd IBCT – Vicenza, Italy, Italy

- Squad Leader in a Light Airborne Infantry Battalion.
- Responsible for the health, welfare, and morale of 4 Senior Line Medics, 15 Platoon Medics and5 Treatment Squad Medics.
- Responsible for the medical readiness and welfare of 800 Paratroopers.
- Coordinated training and sustainment of 20 individuals EMT-B and TC3 certifications Platoon Medic – 2-506th.
- Trained over 100 multinational partners, contractors and foreign nationals on TC3 and FirstAid to develop warfighting and defense capabilities.
- Named 2016 173rd IBCT Best Medic; Competed in US Army Best Medic Competition Awarded
- Expert Field Medical Badge in 2017
- Distinguished Leader Graduate at Advanced Leaders Course

Platoon Medic, 11/2011 to 06/2015

2-506th Infantry Battalion 4th BCT 101st ABN DIV - Fort Campbell, KY

- Responsible for and supervises rapid trauma assessment, triage, treatment, emergencyevacuation and care of battle and disease non-battle injuries.
- Responsible for the readiness and support of 30 Soldiers.
- Administered tests and medication to stabilize patients in field or in transit.
- Administered first aid treatment or life support care to sick or injured persons in prehospital settings.

Valet Supervisor/Valet Attendant, 02/2006 to 11/2011

Towne Park – Monterey, Las Vegas, CA,

- NVDelivers world class guest service.
- Manages the arrivals and departures of all guests.
- Supervised 20 Valet Attendants and responsible for the accountability of up to 400 vehicles parked daily.
- Assigned duties or work schedules to employees for adequate shift coverage.
- Maintained knowledge of business operations to keep departments and employees up to date on important work-related changes.

Education

Associate of Science: Networking Systems Administration, 06/2008

DeVry University - Fremont, CA